Bloodline Killer is a horror, thriller film directed by Ante Novakovic.
Moira Cole endeavors to rebuild her shattered life after her family's
murder at the hands of her deranged and obsessed cousin.
Dr. Lucien, played by Bruce Dern.
Detective Cyphers, played by Tyrese Gibson.
Moira Cole, played by Shawnee Smith.
Sam Marrin, played by Taryn Manning.
Michael Cole, played by Drew Moerlein.
Connor Cole, played by James Gaudioso.
Bloodline Killer is a 2024 American slasher film directed by Ante
Novakovic and written by Anthony and James Gaudioso.
It stars Bruce Dern, Tyrese Gibson,  Shawnee Smith and Taryn Manning.
Filming took place in December 2022 in Connecticut.
It was released on April 26, 2024.
The tone is dark and intense.